Guide to the Merton Stoltz Files 1959-1978
Brown University Library
- Files: 1971-1972, Series 9
  - Academic Departments, Series 9. Subseries B
    - Psychology, 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder IX.53)
    - Religious Studies, 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder IX.54)
- Files: 1972-1973, Series 10
  - General, Series 10. Subseries A
    - Affirmative Action Officer, 1972-1973 (Box 40, Folder X.1)
    - Chaplain's Office, 1972-1973 (Box 40, Folder X.2)
    - Educational Measurement, 1972-1973 (Box 40, Folder X.3)
    - EEO, 1972-1973 (Box 40, Folder X.4)
    - Documents on Brown's Commitment to the Black Community, 1972-1973 (Box 40, Folder X.5)
    - Appendices to document on Reaffirmation on University Commitment to Black Community, 1973 (Box 40, Folder X.6)
    - Extension Division, 1972-1973 (Box 40, Folder X.7)
    - Ford Foundation, 1972-1973 (Box 40, Folder X.8)
    - NSF Undergraduate Institute for Scientific Programs, 1972-1973 (Box 40, Folder X.9)
    - Otto Von Simon, 1972-1973 (Box 40, Folder X.10)
    - John McLaughry (Summer Programs), 1972-1973 (Box 40, Folder X.11)
    - Tougaloo College, 1972-1973 (Box 41, Folder X.12)
    - Untermeyer Fund, 1972-1973 (Box 41, Folder X.13)
  - Academic Departments, Series 10. Subseries B
    - Afro-American Studies, 1972-1973 (Box 41, Folder X.14)
    - Applied Mathematics, 1972-1973 (Box 41, Folder X.15)
    - Committee on Governance and Administration for the Medical School, 1972-1973 (Box 41, Folder X.16)
    - Biological and Medical Sciences, 1972-1973 (Box 41, Folder X.17)
    - Education, 1972-1973 (Box 41, Folder X.18)
    - Engineering, 1972-1973 (Box 41, Folder X.19)
    - English, 1972-1973 (Box 41, Folder X.20)
    - Hispanic and Italian Studies, 1972-1973 (Box 41, Folder X.21)
    - History, 1972-1973 (Box 41, Folder X.22)
    - Libraries, 1972-1973 (Box 41, Folder X.23)
    - Ad Hoc Music Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 41, Folder X.24)
    - Physics, 1972-1973 (Box 41, Folder X.25)
    - Psychology, 1972-1973 (Box 41, Folder X.26)
    - Department of Comparative Literature, 1972 (Box 41, Folder X.27)
- Files: 1973-1974, 1970-1975; Series 11
  - General, Series 11. Subseries A
    - Committee on Awards and Benefits, 1973-1974 (Box 42, Folder XI.1)
    - American University Field Staff (AUFS), 1973-1974 (Box 42, Folder XI.2)
    - Brown University Press, 1973-1974 (Box 42, Folder XI.3)
    - Brown University Press, 1970-1975 (Box 42, Folder XI.4)
    - Chaplain's Office, 1973-1974 (Box 42, Folder XI.5)
    - Institutional Research, 1973-1974 (Box 42, Folder XI.6)
    - John McLaughry (Summer Programs), 1973-1974 (Box 43, Folder XI.7)
    - Promotions and Tenure Recommendations, 1973-1974 (Box 43, Folder XI.8)
    - Tougaloo College, 1970-1975 (Box 43, Folder XI.9)
  - Academic Departments, Series 11. Subseries B
    - Afro-American Studies Program, 1973-1974 (Box 43, Folder XI.10)
    - Applied Mathematics, 1973-1974 (Box 43, Folder XI.11)
    - Bio-Medical Sciences, 1973-1974 (Box 43, Folder XI.12)
    - Biological and Medical Sciences, 1973-1974 (Box 43, Folder XI.13)
    - Chemistry, 1970-1977 (Box 43, Folder XI.14)
    - Computing Laboratory, 1973-1974 (Box 43, Folder XI.15)
    - Economics, 1973-1974 (Box 43, Folder XI.16)
    - Egyptology -- Library, 1973-1974 (Box 43, Folder XI.17)
    - English, 1973-1974 (Box 43, Folder XI.18)
    - Libraries, 1970-1978 (Box 43, Folder XI.19)
    - Music, 1973-1974 (Box 43, Folder XI.20)
    - Religious Studies, 1973-1974 (Box 43, Folder XI.21)
- Files: 1974-1975, 1971-1978; Series 12
  - General, Series 12. Subseries A
    - Braitmayer Foundation 6-38201, 1974-1975 (Box 44, Folder XII.1)
    - Brown U. Excellence Program 6-38182, 1974-1975 (Box 44, Folder XII.2)
    - East Europe Consortium 6-38405, [undated] (Box 44, Folder XII.3)
    - NSF 3711 5-26113, 1974-1975 (Box 44, Folder XII.4)
    - Research Project on East Europe Peasantry 5-29536, 1974-1975 (Box 44, Folder XII.5)
    - University Courses 2-10970, 1974-1975 (Box 44, Folder XII.6)
    - University Professor Instruction 2-10980, 1974-1975 (Box 44, Folder XII.7)
    - Academic Program Development, 1974-1975 (Box 44, Folder XII.8)
    - Admissions, 1974-1975 (Box 44, Folder XII.9)
    - Appointment and Tenure Policy, 1974-1975 (Box 45, Folder XII.10)
    - Awards and Benefits Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 45, Folder XII.11)
    - Brown University Press, 1974-1975 (Box 45, Folder XII.12)
    - Brown-Washington Internship Program, 1974-1975 (Box 45, Folder XII.13)
    - Budget & Personnel, 1974-1975 (Box 45, Folder XII.14)
    - Budget, 1974-1975 (Box 45, Folder XII.15)
    - Budget Change Forms, 1974-1975 (Box 45, Folder XII.16)
    - Benefits, 1974-1975 (Box 45, Folder XII.17)
    - Wage & Salary, 1974-1975 (Box 45, Folder XII.18)
    - Career Development, 1974-1975 (Box 45, Folder XII.19)
    - Chaplain's Office, 1974-1975 (Box 45, Folder XII.20)
    - Commencement, 1974-1975 (Box 45, Folder XII.21)
    - Controller's Office, 1974-1975 (Box 45, Folder XII.22)
    - Endowment Performance Reports, 1974-1975 (Box 45, Folder XII.23)
    - Dean of Academic Affairs, 1974-1975 (Box 45, Folder XII.24)
    - Dean of College, 1974-1975 (Box 46, Folder XII.25)
    - Dean of Graduate School, 1974-1975 (Box 46, Folder XII.26)
    - Development Office, 1974-1975 (Box 46, Folder XII.27)
    - Employment, 1974-1975 (Box 46, Folder XII.28)
    - Extension Division, 1974-1975 (Box 46, Folder XII.29)
    - Faculty Fringe Benefits, 1974-1975 (Box 46, Folder XII.30)
    - Family Education Rights & Privacy Act, 1974-1975 (Box 46, Folder XII.31)
    - Financial Aid, 1974-1975 (Box 46, Folder XII.32)
    - Foreign Studies Office, 1974-1975 (Box 46, Folder XII.33)
    - General Faculty Research Reserve Fund, 1974-1975 (Box 46, Folder XII.34)
    - Government General, 1974-1975 (Box 46, Folder XII.35)
    - Grants & Contracts, 1974-1975 (Box 46, Folder XII.36)
    - Standard Control Forms, 1974-1975 (Box 46, Folder XII.37)
    - Haffenreffer Museum, 1974-1975 (Box 46, Folder XII.38)
    - Health, Education, & Welfare, 1974-1975 (Box 47, Folder XII.39)
    - Suggestions for Honorary Degrees, 1974-1975 (Box 47, Folder XII.40)
    - Hornig, Donald F., 1974-1975 (Box 47, Folder XII.41)
    - Housing Office, 1974-1975 (Box 47, Folder XII.42)
    - Human Studies, 1974-1975 (Box 47, Folder XII.43)
    - IBM Reports, Miscellaneous, 1974-1975 (Box 47, Folder XII.44)
    - International Peace & Development Program Proposal, [undated] (Box 47, Folder XII.45)
    - International Exchange of Persons, 1974-1975 (Box 47, Folder XII.46)
    - ICTOS Proposal, [undated] (Box 47, Folder XII.47)
    - ICTOS Evaluation, 1974-1975 (Box 47, Folder XII.48)
    - Institutional Research, 1974-1975 (Box 47, Folder XII.49)
    - Labor Relations, 1974-1975 (Box 47, Folder XII.50)
    - Latin American Studies Association, 1974-1975 (Box 48, Folder XII.51)
    - Library - Susan A. Ludlum, 1975 (Box 48, Folder XII.52)
    - Maeder, Paul F., 1974-1975 (Box 48, Folder XII.53)
    - McLaughry, John - Summer Programs, 1974-1975 (Box 48, Folder XII.54)
    - Mark IV, 1974-1975 (Box 48, Folder XII.55)
    - Miscellaneous Colleges and Universities, 1974-1975 (Box 48, Folder XII.56)
    - Miscellaneous Matters, 1974-1975 (Box 48, Folder XII.57)
    - MOT Course, 1974-1975 (Box 48, Folder XII.58)
    - Murdoch, Kelsey, 1974-1975 (Box 48, Folder XII.59)
    - National Endowment for Arts & Humanities, 1974-1975 (Box 48, Folder XII.60)
    - NSF, 1974-1975 (Box 48, Folder XII.61)
    - NSF - Institutional Development, 1974-1975 (Box 48, Folder XII.62)
    - NSF - Institutional Development, 1973-1974 (Box 48, Folder XII.63)
    - NSF - Institutional Development, 1972-1973 (Box 48, Folder XII.64)
    - NSF - Institutional Grants, 1971-1972 (Box 49, Folder XII.65)
    - NSF - Institutional Grants, 1974-1975 (Box 49, Folder XII.66)
    - NSF - Materials Research Lab, 1974-1975 (Box 49, Folder XII.67)
    - Physical Plant, 1974-1975 (Box 49, Folder XII.68)
    - Physical Sciences Council, 1974-1975 (Box 49, Folder XII.69)
    - Price, John B., 1974-1975 (Box 49, Folder XII.70)
    - Promotion & Tenure Recommendations, 1974-1975 (Box 49, Folder XII.71)
    - Provost's Office, 1974-1975 (Box 49, Folder XII.72)
    - Provost's Office, 1974-1975 (Box 49, Folder XII.73)
    - Purchasing, 1974-1975 (Box 49, Folder XII.74)
    - Registrar, 1974-1975 (Box 49, Folder XII.75)
    - Rejection of Applicants, 1974-1975 (Box 49, Folder XII.76)
    - Safety Office, 1974-1975 (Box 49, Folder XII.77)
    - Sarah Doyle Center, 1974-1975 (Box 49, Folder XII.78)
    - Security Office, 1974-1975 (Box 49, Folder XII.79)
    - Space Utilization, 1974-1975 (Box 49, Folder XII.80)
    - Staff Meetings, 1974-1975 (Box 49, Folder XII.81)
    - Staffing Plans, 1974-1975 (Box 50, Folder XII.82)
    - Staffing Plans, 1974-1978 (Box 50, Folder XII.83)
    - Stevens, Malcolm S., 1974-1975 (Box 50, Folder XII.84)
    - Student Caucus, 1974-1975 (Box 50, Folder XII.85)
    - Student Coalition, 1974-1975 (Box 50, Folder XII.86)
    - Student Employment, 1974-1975 (Box 50, Folder XII.87)
    - Title IX, 1974-1975 (Box 50, Folder XII.88)
    - Transitional Summer Program, 1974-1975 (Box 50, Folder XII.89)
    - Tuition Benefits, 1974-1975 (Box 50, Folder XII.90)
    - Undergraduate Financial Aid, 1974-1975 (Box 50, Folder XII.91)
    - Wolk, Ronald A., 1974-1975 (Box 51, Folder XII.92)
    - World Studies Data Bank, 1974-1975 (Box 51, Folder XII.93)
  - Academic Departments, Series 12. Subseries B
    - Afro American Studies Program, 1971-1975 (Box 51, Folder XII.94)
    - American Civilization, 1974-1975 (Box 51, Folder XII.95)
    - Anthropology, 1974-1975 (Box 51, Folder XII.96)
    - Applied Mathematics, 1974-1975 (Box 51, Folder XII.97)
    - Art, 1974-1975 (Box 51, Folder XII.98)
    - Art, 1974-1975 (Box 51, Folder XII.99)
    - Asian History, 1974-1975 (Box 51, Folder XII.100)
    - Athletics, 1974-1975 (Box 51, Folder XII.101)
    - Bio-Med Sciences, 1974-1975 (Box 51, Folder XII.102)
    - Chemistry, 1974-1975 (Box 52, Folder XII.103)
    - Classics, 1974-1975 (Box 52, Folder XII.104)
    - Comparative Literature, 1974-1975 (Box 52, Folder XII.105)
    - Computing Lab, 1974-1975 (Box 52, Folder XII.106)
    - Computer Science, 1974-1975 (Box 52, Folder XII.107)
    - Economics, 1974-1975 (Box 52, Folder XII.108)
    - Education, 1974-1975 (Box 52, Folder XII.109)
    - Engineering, 1974-1975 (Box 52, Folder XII.110)
    - English, 1974-1975 (Box 52, Folder XII.111)
    - French Studies, 1974-1975 (Box 52, Folder XII.112)
    - Geological Sciences, 1974-1975 (Box 52, Folder XII.113)
    - German, 1974-1975 (Box 52, Folder XII.114)
    - Hispanic & Italian Studies, 1974-1975 (Box 52, Folder XII.115)
    - History, 1974-1975 (Box 52, Folder XII.116)
    - History of Mathematics, 1974-1975 (Box 53, Folder XII.117)
    - Libraries, 1974-1975 (Box 53, Folder XII.118)
    - Recommendations for Library Budget by Orlando Roncesvalles, 1974 (Box 53, Folder XII.119)
    - John Carter Brown Library, 1974-1975 (Box 53, Folder XII.120)
    - Linguistics, 1974-1975 (Box 53, Folder XII.121)
    - Mathematics, 1974-1975 (Box 53, Folder XII.122)
    - Music, 1974-1975 (Box 53, Folder XII.123)
    - Philosophy, 1974-1975 (Box 53, Folder XII.124)
    - Physics, 1974-1975 (Box 53, Folder XII.125)
    - Department of Physics Chairman, 1974 (Box 53, Folder XII.126)
    - Political Science, 1974-1975 (Box 53, Folder XII.127)
    - Psychology, 1974-1975 (Box 53, Folder XII.128)
    - John Stein - Psychology, 1975-1976 (Box 53, Folder XII.129)
    - Religious Studies, 1974-1975 (Box 53, Folder XII.130)
    - Renaissance Studies, 1974-1975 (Box 53, Folder XII.131)
    - Slavic Languages, 1974-1975 (Box 53, Folder XII.132)
    - Social Psychology, 1974-1975 (Box 53, Folder XII.133)
    - Sociology, 1974-1975 (Box 53, Folder XII.134)
    - Urban Studies, 1974-1975 (Box 53, Folder XII.135)
    - Urban Studies, 1974-1975 (Box 53, Folder XII.136)
- Files: 1975-1976, 1973-1976; Series 13
  - General, Series 13. Subseries A
    - Provost - 2-30180, 1973-1975 (Box 54, Folder XIII.1)
    - Braitmayer Foundation - 6-38201, 1975-1976 (Box 54, Folder XIII.2)
    - Brown U. Excellence Program - 6-38182, 1975-1976 (Box 54, Folder XIII.3)
    - Human Studies - 2-10460, 1975-1976 (Box 54, Folder XIII.4)
    - IBM Reports - Miscellaneous, 1975-1976 (Box 54, Folder XIII.5)
    - NSF #3711 - 5-26113, 1975-1976 (Box 54, Folder XIII.6)
    - Physical Sciences Council - 2-30190, 1976 (Box 54, Folder XIII.7)
    - Provost Contingency Fund - 2-39755, 1975-1976 (Box 55, Folder XIII.8)
    - Univ. Prof. Instruction - 2-10980, 1975-1976 (Box 55, Folder XIII.9)
    - Academic Program Development (Bert Hill), 1975-1976 (Box 55, Folder XIII.10)
    - Admissions, 1975-1976 (Box 55, Folder XIII.11)
    - Information on Admissions & Financial Aid for Class of 1980, 1976 (Box 55, Folder XIII.12)
    - M.R.L. - Proposed Advisory Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 55, Folder XIII.13)
    - Brown Daily Herald, 1975-1976 (Box 55, Folder XIII.14)
    - Brown University Press, 1975-1976 (Box 55, Folder XIII.15)
    - Budget Material for Budget Year 1975/76, 1974-1976 (Box 55, Folder XIII.16)
    - Budget Office - General, 1975-1976 (Box 55, Folder XIII.17)
    - Budget Office - Benefits, 1975-1976 (Box 56, Folder XIII.18)
    - Budget Office - Change Forms, 1975-1976 (Box 56, Folder XIII.19)
    - Budget Office - Employment, 1975-1976 (Box 56, Folder XIII.20)
    - Budget Office - Personnel, 1975-1976 (Box 56, Folder XIII.21)
    - Budget Office - Records, 1975-1976 (Box 56, Folder XIII.22)
    - Budget Office - Wage & Salary, 1975-1976 (Box 56, Folder XIII.23)
    - Chaplain's Office, 1975-1976 (Box 56, Folder XIII.24)
    - Commencement, 1975-1976 (Box 56, Folder XIII.25)
    - C.O.F.H.E., 1975-1976 (Box 56, Folder XIII.26)
    - Commonwealth Fund (Interface Program), 1975-1976 (Box 56, Folder XIII.27)
    - Controller's Office, 1975-1976 (Box 56, Folder XIII.28)
    - Dean of the College, 1975-1976 (Box 56, Folder XIII.29)
    - Dean of Faculty and Academic Affairs, 1975-1976 (Box 56, Folder XIII.30)
    - Dean of Graduate School, 1975-1976 (Box 57, Folder XIII.31)
    - Development Office, 1975-1976 (Box 57, Folder XIII.32)
    - Extension Division, 1975-1976 (Box 57, Folder XIII.33)
    - Financial Aid Office, 1975-1976 (Box 57, Folder XIII.34)
    - Foreign Studies Office, 1975-1976 (Box 57, Folder XIII.35)
    - Grants & Contracts Office, 1975-1976 (Box 57, Folder XIII.36)
    - Health, Education & Welfare, 1975-1976 (Box 57, Folder XIII.37)
    - Modern Foreign Language Training and Area Studies, 1975-1976 (Box 57, Folder XIII.38)
    - Suggestions for Honorary Degrees, 1975-1976 (Box 57, Folder XIII.39)
    - Hornig, Donald F., 1975-1976 (Box 57, Folder XIII.40)
    - Housing Office, 1975-1976 (Box 57, Folder XIII.41)
    - Information on 2nd Class Catalog Mailings, 1975-1976 (Box 57, Folder XIII.42)
    - Institutional Research, 1975-1976 (Box 57, Folder XIII.43)
    - International Exchange of Persons, 1975-1976 (Box 58, Folder XIII.44)
    - Interstate Compact for Education, 1976 (Box 58, Folder XIII.45)
    - Maeder, Paul F., 1975-1976 (Box 58, Folder XIII.46)
    - McLaughry, John - Summer Programs, 1975-1976 (Box 58, Folder XIII.47)
    - Miscellaneous - Colleges & Universities, 1975-1976 (Box 58, Folder XIII.48)
    - Miscellaneous, 1975-1976 (Box 58, Folder XIII.49)
    - Murdoch, Kelsey - Asst. to the President, 1975-1976 (Box 58, Folder XIII.50)
    - National Endowment for the Arts & Humanities, 1975-1976 (Box 58, Folder XIII.51)
    - NSF - General, 1975-1976 (Box 58, Folder XIII.52)
    - NSF - Institutional Development, 1975-1976 (Box 58, Folder XIII.53)
    - NSF - Institutional Grants, 1975-1976 (Box 58, Folder XIII.54)
    - Material research Laboratory, 1975-1976 (Box 59, Folder XIII.55)
    - ICTOS Program, 1974-1976 (Box 59, Folder XIII.56)
    - ICTOS Program, 1975-1976 (Box 59, Folder XIII.57)
    - Presidential Search Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 59, Folder XIII.58)
    - Price, John B., 1975-1976 (Box 59, Folder XIII.59)
    - Program and Research Development, 1974-1975 (Box 59, Folder XIII.60)
    - Program and Research Development, 1974-1975 (Box 60, Folder XIII.60A)
    - Provost's Office, 1975-1976 (Box 61, Folder XIII.61)
    - Registrar's Office (M.E. Noble), 1975-1976 (Box 61, Folder XIII.62)
    - Rejection of Applicants, 1975-1976 (Box 61, Folder XIII.63)
    - R.I. Public Higher Education Agency, 1975-1976 (Box 61, Folder XIII.64)
    - Sabbatical Leave Reports, 1975-1976 (Box 61, Folder XIII.65)
    - Sankore, 1974-1975 (Box 61, Folder XIII.66)
    - Staffing Plan Projections, 1975-1976 (Box 61, Folder XIII.67)
    - Student Employment, 1975-1976 (Box 61, Folder XIII.68)
    - Wolk, Ronald A., 1975-1976 (Box 61, Folder XIII.69)
    - Women's Organizations - Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 61, Folder XIII.70)
  - Academic Departments, Series 13. Subseries B
    - Afro American Studies Program, 1975-1976 (Box 61, Folder XIII.71)
    - Anthropology, 1975-1976 (Box 61, Folder XIII.72)
    - Applied Mathematics, 1975-1976 (Box 61, Folder XIII.73)
    - Art, 1975-1976 (Box 62, Folder XIII.74)
    - Athletics, 1975-1976 (Box 62, Folder XIII.75)
    - Bio-Med Sciences, 1975-1976 (Box 62, Folder XIII.76)
    - Medical Council, 1975-1976 (Box 62, Folder XIII.77)
    - Chemistry, 1975-1976 (Box 62, Folder XIII.78)
    - Classics, 1975-1976 (Box 62, Folder XIII.79)
    - Comparative Literature, 1975-1976 (Box 62, Folder XIII.80)
    - Computing Lab, 1975-1976 (Box 62, Folder XIII.81)
    - Economics, 1975-1976 (Box 62, Folder XIII.82)
    - Education, 1975-1976 (Box 62, Folder XIII.83)
    - Engineering, 1975-1976 (Box 62, Folder XIII.84)
    - English, 1975-1976 (Box 62, Folder XIII.85)
    - Proposal to CBS, 1975-1976 (Box 62, Folder XIII.86)
    - French Studies, 1975-1976 (Box 62, Folder XIII.87)
    - Durand, Promotion Information, 1975-1976 (Box 62, Folder XIII.88)
    - Geological Sciences, 1975-1976 (Box 62, Folder XIII.89)
    - German, 1975-1976 (Box 62, Folder XIII.90)
    - Hispanic & Italian Studies, 1975-1976 (Box 62, Folder XIII.91)
    - History, 1975-1976 (Box 62, Folder XIII.92)
    - History of Mathematics, 1975-1976 (Box 62, Folder XIII.93)
    - Libraries, 1975-1976 (Box 63, Folder XIII.94)
    - Annmary Brown Memorial Committee of Management, 1975-1976 (Box 63, Folder XIII.95)
    - Special Collections, 1976 (Box 63, Folder XIII.96)
    - Library Budget Information, 1975-1976 (Box 63, Folder XIII.97)
    - Linguistics, 1975-1976 (Box 63, Folder XIII.98)
    - Music, 1975-1976 (Box 63, Folder XIII.99)
    - Physics, 1975-1976 (Box 63, Folder XIII.100)
    - Political Science, 1975-1976 (Box 63, Folder XIII.101)
    - Religious Studies, 1975-1976 (Box 63, Folder XIII.102)
    - Renaissance Studies, 1975-1976 (Box 63, Folder XIII.103)
    - Sociology, 1975-1976 (Box 63, Folder XIII.104)
    - Slavic Languages, 1975-1976 (Box 63, Folder XIII.105)
    - East European Studies, [undated] (Box 63, Folder XIII.106)
    - Information on OIR Director Search, 1975-1976 (Box 63, Folder XIII.107)
    - Information on OIR Director Search, 1975-1976 (Box 63, Folder XIII.108)
    - Information on OIR Director Search, 1975 (Box 64, Folder XIII.109)
    - Information on OIR Director Search, 1975-1976 (Box 64, Folder XIII.110)
    - Zimmer Proposal - Impact of Changing Community Structure, 1975 (Box 64, Folder XIII.111)
    - Draft Memo on Health & Society Program, 1975 (Box 64, Folder XIII.112)
- Files: 1976-1977, 1975-1977; Series 14
  - General, Series 14. Subseries A
    - Provost's Account 2-30180, 1976-1977 (Box 65, Folder XIV.1)
    - Provost's Special account 2-30181, 1975-1977 (Box 65, Folder XIV.2)
    - Provost's Contingency Account 2-39755, 1976-1977 (Box 65, Folder XIV.3)
    - Braitmayer Foundation 6-38201, 1976-1977 (Box 65, Folder XIV.4)
    - East European Consortium 6-38405, 1976-1977 (Box 65, Folder XIV.5)
    - B.U. Excellence Program 6-38182, 1976-1977 (Box 65, Folder XIV.6)
    - East European Peasantry 5-29536, 1976-1977 (Box 65, Folder XIV.7)
    - NSF #3711 - 5-26113, 1976-1977 (Box 66, Folder XIV.8)
    - Miscellaneous Accounts, 1976-1977 (Box 66, Folder XIV.9)
    - Academic Program Development - Bert Hill, 1976-1977 (Box 66, Folder XIV.10)
    - Acting President Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 66, Folder XIV.11)
    - Admissions Office, 1976-1977 (Box 66, Folder XIV.12)
    - Admission Policy Statement - H.R. Swearer, 1977 (Box 66, Folder XIV.13)
    - Admission Recruitment Policy, 1977 (Box 67, Folder XIV.14)
    - Anti-Defamation League - B'nai B'rith, 1976 (Box 67, Folder XIV.15)
    - Association of American Universities, 1976-1977 (Box 67, Folder XIV.16)
    - Brown University Press, 1976-1977 (Box 67, Folder XIV.17)
    - Budget Office - General, 1976-1977 (Box 67, Folder XIV.18)
    - Benefits, 1976-1977 (Box 67, Folder XIV.19)
    - Change Forms, 1976-1977 (Box 67, Folder XIV.20)
    - Employment, 1976-1977 (Box 67, Folder XIV.21)
    - Labor Relations, 1976-1977 (Box 67, Folder XIV.22)
    - Time Sheets for Semi-Monthly Non-Exempt Employees, 1976-1977 (Box 68, Folder XIV.23)
    - Personnel Notices, 1976-1977 (Box 68, Folder XIV.24)
    - Wage & salary, 1976-1977 (Box 68, Folder XIV.25)
    - Budget Requests, 1976-1977 (Box 68, Folder XIV.26)
    - Chaplain's Office, 1976-1977 (Box 68, Folder XIV.27)
    - Foreign Student & Faculty Office, 1976-1977 (Box 68, Folder XIV.28)
    - Commencement, 1976-1977 (Box 68, Folder XIV.29)
    - Controller's Office, 1976-1977 (Box 68, Folder XIV.30)
    - Dean of the College, 1976-1977 (Box 68, Folder XIV.31)
    - Dean of the Faculty and Academic Affairs, 1976-1977 (Box 68, Folder XIV.32)
    - Dean of the Graduate School, 1976-1977 (Box 68, Folder XIV.33)
    - Development Office, 1976-1977 (Box 69, Folder XIV.34)
    - Equal Opportunity Office, 1976-1977 (Box 69, Folder XIV.35)
    - Farview, Inc., 1976-1977 (Box 69, Folder XIV.36)
    - Financial Aid, 1976-1977 (Box 69, Folder XIV.37)
    - Financial Aid Statistics, 1976-1977 (Box 69, Folder XIV.38)
    - Health, Education & Welfare, 1976-1977 (Box 69, Folder XIV.39)
    - Suggestions for Honorary Degrees, 1976-1977 (Box 69, Folder XIV.40)
    - Institutional Research, 1976-1977 (Box 70, Folder XIV.41)
    - Instructional Time Bank, 1976-1977 (Box 70, Folder XIV.42)
    - International Exchange of Scholars, 1976-1977 (Box 70, Folder XIV.43)
    - Maeder, Paul F., 1976-1977 (Box 70, Folder XIV.44)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence - Campus, 1976-1977 (Box 70, Folder XIV.45)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence - Colleges and Universities, 1976-1977 (Box 70, Folder XIV.46)
    - Murdoch, Kelsey, 1976-1977 (Box 70, Folder XIV.47)
    - National Alumni Schools Program, 1976-1977 (Box 70, Folder XIV.48)
    - National Association of Independent Colleges & Universities, 1976-1977 (Box 70, Folder XIV.49)
    - National Science Foundation - General, 1976-1977 (Box 70, Folder XIV.50)
    - Materials Research Laboratory, 1976-1977 (Box 70, Folder XIV.51)
    - National Solar Energy Research Consortium and SERI, 1975-1977 (Box 70, Folder XIV.52)
    - Presidential Search Information, 1976-1977 (Box 71, Folder XIV.53)
    - Provost's Office, 1976-1977 (Box 71, Folder XIV.54)
    - Purchasing Office, 1976-1977 (Box 71, Folder XIV.55)
    - Registrar's Office, 1976-1977 (Box 71, Folder XIV.56)
    - Rejection of Applicants, 1976-1977 (Box 71, Folder XIV.57)
    - Requests for Publications, 1976-1977 (Box 71, Folder XIV.58)
    - Research Administration Office (Grants and Contracts), 1976-1977 (Box 71, Folder XIV.59)
    - R. I. Higher Education Council, 1976-1977 (Box 71, Folder XIV.60)
    - Safety Office, 1976-1977 (Box 71, Folder XIV.61)
    - Strike-Related Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 71, Folder XIV.62)
    - Strike-Related Correspondence, 1976 (Box 72, Folder XIV.63)